liberty-bank.com 2002-06-02

# Liberty Bank Privacy Notice

At Liberty Bank, your privacy is a top priority. 

As our customer, you necessarily provide us with certain personal information about yourself. We take very seriously our obligation to safeguard the privacy of that information. 

The personal data you give us are used to administer your accounts in a professional and efficient manner, to provide you with excellent service, and to develop and offer financial services designed to meet your needs. **We do not sell your personal information to anyone, for any purpose.**

On this page, you will find details about our policy on privacy and about how personal information about you is collected and used. If you have any questions, please contact our Customer Service Center at (888) 570-0773. 

Liberty Bank has been privileged to serve our customers for 176 years because we have earned your trust. We are committed to maintaining that trust by ensuring the confidentiality of your personal information. 

**The Liberty Bank Privacy Policy**

The privacy policies described on this page apply to both Liberty Bank and its affiliates, Liberty Bank Mortgage Corporation and Community Realty Investors, Inc. Throughout this policy, the phrase "personal information" refers to nonpublic personal information that identifies you. 

**We do not sell your personal information to anyone.**

 **What do we mean when we say "personal information"?**

In the process of providing you with financial products and services, we collect certain personal information about you, including: 

| Information that you provide to us on applications and other forms (including those on our web site), such as your name, address, date of birth, telephone and Social Security numbers, assets, debts, and income.  
---|---  
| Information from credit reporting agencies regarding your credit history or creditworthiness.  
| Information about you that we acquire from other third parties to assist us in evaluating your application for Liberty Bank products and services; for example, employment status that we obtain to determine your eligibility for a loan.  
| Information about your transactions with Liberty Bank and our affiliates; for example, your account balances, payment history, and transaction details.  
  
**We do not share your personal information with third parties not affiliated with Liberty except under the following circumstances:**

| We disclose personal information as necessary to facilitate transactions; for example, to collect a check.  
---|---  
| We share personal information with companies that perform services for us; for example, check printing, data processing, and mailing.  
| To keep you informed about products and services, we may also, as legally permitted, disclose personal information to companies that assist us in marketing, including other financial institutions with whom we have agreements.  
| We also disclose personal information as required or permitted by law; for example, in response to a subpoena or garnishment, or to a credit bureau. 

**Except in the circumstances above, we do not share your personal information with third parties not affiliated with Liberty unless you expressly permit us to do so.** Transaction and experience information, such as your account balance, payment history, and transaction details, may be shared between us and our affiliates, as allowed by the Fair Credit Reporting Act.  
  
**Your personal information is kept confidential.**

We have developed procedural, electronic, and physical safeguards to protect your privacy in accordance with federal standards. We have designed procedures to restrict access to your personal information to those employees who need to know it in order to provide products or services to you, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of this information. 

**The protections of our privacy policy are extended to former customers as well as current ones.**

**We’ll keep you informed of changes to our privacy policy.**

If our policy changes in the future, the new policy will be posted on our web site, and you will be notified in writing of the changes. 

* * *

**Your Privacy Online - for Internet Users**

**Our privacy policy also safeguards your online interactions with Liberty Bank.**

The information age has made online banking easy and convenient. You can visit our web site with confidence, knowing that we are as committed to your privacy and security online as we are in more traditional banking settings. 

**LibertyLink Internet Banking Security**

Protecting the confidentiality and security of your personal and account information is top priority at Liberty. Months of research and state-of-the-art technology have gone into ensuring that your LibertyLink transactions are secure. But your cooperation is vital to maximize the effectiveness of our security measures. Here are some steps you should take to protect the privacy of information you send and receive when you use LibertyLink: 

In general, be careful of any Internet site with which you are not familiar. Avoid sending information like your Social Security number, credit card numbers, or bank account information unless you are in a secure site like LibertyLink. When visiting new sites, be particularly aware of small windows that may randomly appear on the screen. If you are not comfortable with a newly-created window, close it immediately. The safest next step would be to exit and restart your browser. 

**Contacting Liberty Via E-mail**

Liberty Bank offers several ways of contacting the bank using electronic mail. 

**Here are some "do’s" and "don’ts" for contacting Liberty Bank electronically:**

**Links to Non-Liberty Bank Web Sites**

We provide links to other web sites that offer non-Liberty Bank services, products, or information that we think may be of interest to you. It’s important that you review the privacy policies of these sites, since we cannot control the information provided or the information collection practices of any non-Liberty Bank site you visit. We do not guarantee or endorse any of the services, products, or information provided through these sites. 

**Online Privacy And Children**

In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information about children under the age of thirteen. 

**Calculators**

The calculators on our web site do not store any personal information when you use them. 

**Changes in Our Online Privacy Policy**

We are continually reviewing new technological developments in our efforts to provide you with a high level of online security and privacy when you use our web site. If our online privacy protections are revised, we will update this policy to reflect any changes. 

**Questions?**

**If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please[Contact Us](https://www.liberty-bank.com/contactus/), or call our Customer Service Center at (888) 570-0773.**
